https://www.queenberry.com/privacy.php?osCsid=av9rvo9d1mbkhuqsgckfoj87m4

×CartMy Wish List
Browse Categories  Personalized Engraving  Bracelets  Necklaces  Key Chains  Pet ID  Wallet Cards  Others  Charms Club  European Charm Bracelets  Bracelets / Bangles  Earrings  Necklaces & Pendants  Leather Necklace / Choker  Leather Necklace w/ Pendant  Others Necklaces / Pendants  Sterling Silver Necklace  Jewelry Sets  Brooches / Rings / Others  Bracelets - Others  Gemstones Series  Pearl Series  Swarovski Bangle Bracelet  Swarovski Chain Bracelet  Swarovski Charm Bracelet  Swarovski Tennis Bracelet I  Swarovski Tennis Bracelet II  Swarovski Tennis Flower  Vintage Silver Bracelet  Oriental Charm Bracelet  Lampwork/clay Series  Pendants  Cross  Diamond  Fancy Stones  Heart  Leaf  New Moon  Oval  Pear-Shaped  Seashell  Snowflake  Sphere  Star  Teardrop  Men's Jewelry  Bracelets  Necklaces  Kids' Collection  Anklets  Freshwater Pearl  Bracelets  Earrings  Necklace  Rings  Rings
Payment Method
Shipping
Return & Exchange
Privacy Notice
Contact Us
Links
Home
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
Queenberry.com, is committed to maintaining your confidence and trust;
we accordingly maintain the following privacy policy to protect personal information.
It is our policy that personal information, such as your name, postal and e-mail address, credit card info or telephone number, is private and confidential. Accordingly, the personal information you provide is stored in a secure location accessible only by designated staffs
and is used only for the purposes for which you provide the information (such as to reply to your request or to handle your warranty claim).
For example, when you file a warranty claim online, the personal information you provide will be used to process your complaint.
If you also indicate on our sites that you would like to receive information about other our products and services, such as special offer or membership, your personal information will be added to appropriate queenberry.com mailing lists.
No Release of Information to Third Parties
Your personal information will not be released to third parties except to further the purpose for which you provide the information,
such as sending your complaint to our suppliers for action, or if release is required by law or is pertinent to judicial or governmental investigations or proceedings.
There are no other circumstances under which we will provide or sell personal information of our customers to third parties.
Copyright © 2002 - 2020 queenberry.com. All Rights Reserved. No images may be copied or downloaded from this site without written permission.
FREE US SHIPPING
